<w:body xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main"><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00CF61FE" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="aa" /><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>Research on the Development of Sports Education Orientation under the Background of Sunshine Sports and Quality Education</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidRPr="008C00E2" w:rsidR="008C00E2" w:rsidP="008C00E2" w:rsidRDefault="008C00E2"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPAbstract" /><w:jc w:val="center" /><w:rPr><w:sz w:val="28" /><w:szCs w:val="28" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:sz w:val="28" /><w:szCs w:val="28" /></w:rPr><w:t>Song,Kyungmin</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidRPr="008C00E2"><w:rPr><w:sz w:val="28" /><w:szCs w:val="28" /><w:vertAlign w:val="superscript" /></w:rPr><w:t>1</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008C00E2" w:rsidP="008C00E2" w:rsidRDefault="008C00E2"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPAbstract" /><w:jc w:val="center" /><w:rPr><w:sz w:val="28" /><w:szCs w:val="28" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r w:rsidRPr="008C00E2"><w:rPr><w:sz w:val="28" /><w:szCs w:val="28" /><w:vertAlign w:val="superscript" /></w:rPr><w:t>1</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidRPr="008C00E2"><w:rPr><w:sz w:val="28" /><w:szCs w:val="28" /></w:rPr><w:t>Gachon University, Seongnam, KOREA</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidRPr="006C77F8" w:rsidR="008F0488" w:rsidP="006C77F8" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="2" /></w:pPr><w:r w:rsidRPr="006C77F8"><w:t>Abstract</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="008C00E2" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPAbstract" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="de-DE" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:b /><w:bCs /><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="de-DE" /></w:rPr><w:t>In this paper, we conduct research on the development of the sports education orientation under the background of the sunshine sports and quality education</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">. The reform of the college sports curriculum system structure and development direction lies in the effective use of basic innovative elements, the university sports curriculum structure on thought transformation, the characteristic of the sports development in the important position in university, highlight the advantages of physical education curriculum system structure. The innovation of the university sports curriculum structure is mainly embodied in the curriculum structure layout is reasonable, the new courses and traditional courses for effective integration could reflect the era development elements and innovative ideas of the curriculum building, sports development to provide broad platform for colleges and universities. Our research proposes the innovative perspective of the reform with the assistance of </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="de-DE" /></w:rPr><w:t>sunshine sports and quality education that will enhance the further development of the teaching patterns.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="006C77F8" w:rsidP="006C77F8" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="3" /><w:rPr><w:b w:val="0" /><w:bCs w:val="0" /><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:sz w:val="24" /><w:szCs w:val="24" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:sz w:val="24" /><w:szCs w:val="24" /></w:rPr><w:t>Keywords</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPKeywords" /><w:rPr><w:rFonts w:ascii="Times New Roman" w:hAnsi="Times New Roman" w:cs="Times New Roman" /><w:b /><w:bCs /><w:i /><w:iCs /><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:sz w:val="24" /><w:szCs w:val="24" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:rFonts w:ascii="Times New Roman" w:hAnsi="Times New Roman" w:cs="Times New Roman" /><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:sz w:val="24" /><w:szCs w:val="24" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve"> Sports Education, Sunshine Sports, Quality Education, Development Orientation</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00F97010" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="2" /></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">1 </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:t>Introduction</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>Physical education curriculum guiding ideology and core curriculum goal is to build and support the essential elements of physical education curriculum mode, the former is based on the essence of the sports, physical education and social formation to train a person's overall request, such as the health education, life-long physical education and quality education, innovative education and so on, thus build the theoretical basis of sports curriculum pattern. The embodiment of course goal is the guiding ideology, is the starting point of curriculum development and the important basis of teaching practice. The content of physical education curriculum is guiding ideology and achieves the teaching goal of the carrier that is the teaching process teachers teaching, student learning practice object to its overall framework sports courses through the course content. Physical education curriculum implementation process mainly refers to the teachers and the students according to certain methods and procedures to implement the teaching activities, so as to realize the basic teaching effect. Learning evaluation is to promote teaching activities, the main method to examine the effects of teaching, evaluation feedback function is indispensable to sports new curriculum pattern is an important part</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="0032159A"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="begin" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="0032159A"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:instrText xml:space="preserve"> REF _Ref469046486 \r \h </w:instrText></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="0032159A"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="0032159A"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="separate" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="0032159A"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>[1]</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="0032159A"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="end" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="0032159A"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="begin" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="0032159A"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:instrText xml:space="preserve"> REF _Ref469046488 \r \h </w:instrText></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="0032159A"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="0032159A"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="separate" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="0032159A"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>[2]</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="0032159A"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="end" /></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>The idea of college sports curriculum system constructing could be roughly summarized as the list of the aspects. (1) The formation process of all things is in the process of continuous development, to be completed, and there will be some innovation in the process of mutual fusion, which satisfy the general law of the development of things. In the colleges and universities sports curriculum system constructing "development" as the center to promote university sports curriculum system constructing gradually "innovation", and making the innovation elements and produce the inevitable link between college sports curriculum development, therefore, to push each other and obtain promote together. (2) Innovation points of view, the process of the construction of the university sports curriculum system the main innovative ideas, innovative curriculum management mechanism, the innovation curriculum setting, curriculum integration, etc. These are to promote college sports curriculum system to form the fundamental as is the university sports scientific and standardized management and implementation of the necessary conditions under the state-of-the-</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="007353E6"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">art guidelines of perspectives </w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="007353E6"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="begin" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="007353E6"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:instrText xml:space="preserve"> REF _Ref469046513 \r \h </w:instrText></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="007353E6"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="007353E6"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="separate" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="007353E6"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>[3]</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="007353E6"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="end" /></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>Quality education is to improve the students' basic quality, promote the students' physical and core mental development to develop the wisdom potential, the formation of students' healthy personality. Sports has a unique role in quality education is also a measure of a school education quality standards that cannot be ignored and this effect was compared to other disciplines. The basic status of physical education in school is determined by the social demand for education school physical education is an important part of school education which is the important content of the quality education. Sports in quality-oriented education, has he irreplaceable role, the teaching can help students mental, physical development, cultivate students' competitive consciousness, enterprising spirit and healthy aesthetic view, strengthen students' memory, imagination, trains the student to overcome the difficulties of the perseverance and unity cooperation spirit that causes the student to have the most basic personality characteristics. The figure one demonstrates the mentioned principles.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="DrawingParagraph"><w:bookmarkStart w:name="E:\Journal/image/art%3A10.1186%2Fs12879-015-1235-y/MediaObjects/12879_015_1235_Fig1_HTML.png" w:id="rId8" /><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="0" /></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:ind w:firstLine="0" /><w:jc w:val="center" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">Figure1. The </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>s</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">ystematic </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>d</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">escription of the </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>c</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">ontemporary </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>p</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">hysical </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>e</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">ducation </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>s</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>ystem</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>In this paper, we conduct research on the development of the sports education orientation under the background of sunshine sports and quality education. Sport is an integral part of modern education as it is different from the other science physical education was based on the physical exercise of the basic method of a kind of the practical education. Therefore It can achieve many of the education effect is irreplaceable by the other disciplines, it besides fitness function, at least there are a lot of function and role. We will theoretically analyze the issues in the later sections.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00826DB5" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="2" /><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>2 The proposed methodology and perspective</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00C17127" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="3" /><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>2.1 The features of the sunshine sports</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraph1st" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>Sunshine sports as a country to promote the youth physical fitness and a major move, it embodies our country strengthen students' physical fitness to promote the development of the school physical education and the construction of the sports power conviction and determination. In modern colleges and universities under the framework of the management system, sports system, how to make college sunshine sports content is clear, standard form and ran smoothly needs further discussion. This article mainly is sunlight sports in colleges and universities monitoring system research on the related issue, aims to build a monitoring system in conformity with the nature of the sunlight sports in colleges and universities</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="00DE3CDB"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="begin" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="00DE3CDB"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:instrText xml:space="preserve"> REF _Ref469046525 \r \h </w:instrText></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="00DE3CDB"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="00DE3CDB"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="separate" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="00DE3CDB"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>[4]</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="00DE3CDB"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="end" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="00DE3CDB"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="begin" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="00DE3CDB"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:instrText xml:space="preserve"> REF _Ref469046527 \r \h </w:instrText></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="00DE3CDB"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="00DE3CDB"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="separate" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="00DE3CDB"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>[5]</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="00DE3CDB"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="end" /></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>After reviewing the state-of-the-art research on the sunshine sport, we could find major drawbacks as the following categories. (1) Repeated research, innovation research. Sunshine sports study is a new research topic, regardless of the primary theory of development needs, and practice the objective requirements are supposed to have a lot of research contents, wide range of research from different angles and is a very urgent task and some of current research, it is keen to pursue the so-called "hot spots", the utility to "copy" or "transplant" sunshine sports development survey in some areas, once appear, the regional research results immediately to follow the suit. (2) Implement research, theory building research. Theory, for the moment, and study the urgent, derived from the sunlight sports practice has the overall situation, a long-term and strategic point of view, and build a theory system, such as the sunlight sports marketing model, less of sunshine sports development of the long-acting mechanism. (3) Countermeasure research theoretical research is less. Sports theory of sunshine sports conducted in-depth research, focuses on overall exists the countermeasure research while ignore the phenomenon common basic theory research, theoretical research lag is very outstanding and the false himself, theoretical research demonstration system as the lack of logic and theory support.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>The sunlight sports is not only make students consciously learn to exercise, it also emphasizes how to exercise, as will exercise into our own life. For students, the healthy sports activities are not only to teach them how to correctly use PE material, understand the sports rules, but also teach them how to get along with others in the process of sports. The sunlight sports is a kind of lifetime sports values, is not a form of school sports. Sunshine sports should be to guide the student lifelong sports concept of internalization and explicit physical exercise habits, and internalization and explicit in the different student individual reflects the strong subjectivity. Sunshine sports monitoring system of colleges and universities should eventually point on the improvement of students' physique and sports habits.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="006509F3" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="3" /><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>2.2 The Sports Education Pattern</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraph1st" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>In the work of scholastic physical education, the teaching is the important link. The syllabus and teaching materials is the main part of the curriculum construction link, should be scientific and feasible line sports lifelong pursuit to reflect the goal of sports teaching and the characteristics of the region. In the figure two we show the principles</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="004B004C"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="begin" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="004B004C"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:instrText xml:space="preserve"> REF _Ref469046539 \r \h </w:instrText></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="004B004C"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="004B004C"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="separate" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="004B004C"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>[6]</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="004B004C"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="end" /></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="DrawingParagraph"><w:bookmarkStart w:name="E:\Journal/image/art%3A10.1186%2Fs12879-015-1235-y/MediaObjects/12879_015_1235_Fig2_HTML.png" w:id="rId9" /><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="0" /></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:ind w:firstLine="0" /><w:jc w:val="center" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">Figure2. The </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>l</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">earning </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>c</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">ircle for </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>r</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">eference of the </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>p</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">hysical </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>e</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">ducation </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>p</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>rocedures</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraph1st" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>Sports and health teaching goal is the starting point and end-result of PE teaching activities as is a very important sport teaching theory and practice problem. Compared with other subjects teaching, sports teaching in addition to the characteristics of education theory and method of the same and its own unique characteristics are demonstrated as follows.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="1" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>Sports teaching content diversity, determines the teaching model must be connected to the teaching content to adapt to, and to the law of the different sports skills for teaching basis to establish the corresponding education mode</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="004B004C"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="begin" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="004B004C"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:instrText xml:space="preserve"> REF _Ref469046554 \r \h </w:instrText></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="004B004C"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="004B004C"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="separate" /></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="004B004C"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>[7]</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidR="004B004C"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:fldChar w:fldCharType="end" /></w:r><w:bookmarkStart w:name="_GoBack" w:id="0" /><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="0" /><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="1" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>Organize sports teaching physical education teachers in the larger space, not only should teach sports knowledge, techniques and skills, but also organizes the student to master the necessary knowledge through physical exercises, etc.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="1" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>Sport teaching is in a relatively open space within the bilateral activity, the students' learning is in the scope of "move" under the condition of larger and many non-intellectual factors will influence the general and overall teaching effect.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="1" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>Sports teaching is based on physical exercises as the main means of skill acquisition activity, is in the physical activity and thinking activity in the process of the combination of master the knowledge and skills. Physical education teaching mode, therefore, should not only reflect the regularity of formation of motor skills, also want to reflect physical activity of human body physiology activity changes in laws, and they follow rules of learning of recognizing things.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00FE4EB1" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="3" /><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>2.3 The Quality Education</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraph1st" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>The sports teaching objects are all students, that is, sports teaching reform should be geared to the needs of all students, namely implement quality education for all students. No there is no such thing as quality education in the whole education. The first goal of the reform of the physical education teaching is: to make sports really belongs to the students, for all the students' physical and psychological quality development services and to achieve this goal, the teachers should change ideas and teaching methods, and further study of theory of curriculum reform and the guiding ideology, fundamentally improve education teaching methods and strategies to improve the students' interest in learning. Let the students take an active part in the whole process of the sports teaching activity, the physical education truly form, with god, let all the students in the training of physical quality effectively at the same time that has also been physical and mental health development.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraph1st" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>In order to effectively promote the formation of the national fitness to improve the comprehensive quality of talent education, speed up the construction of China's sports power, we should try to solve the current problems existing in the education of physical education in our country, actively carry out and implement the policy of quality education reform in our country, and take the various measures to promote the reform of the education of physical education in China. Under this guidance, we should focus on the issues of the following aspects. (1)  Strengthen PE teachers' motivation and improve the level of sports teachers. Under the quality education of higher vocational education of physical culture and sports shall be fully respected and the certain sports teachers to strengthen the physical education teachers of material incentive and spiritual incentive, prompting them to the consciously and actively improve the teachers level, for the reform of physical education to lay a solid professional foundation. Specific special interest in sports course can be considered as a PE teacher incentive standard, i.e., according to the physical education teachers with interest classes and various tasks will registration number as the number of the performance salary standard of appraisal. (2) Attaches great importance to physical education, and gradually increase the funds investment. Participate in school sports education in higher vocational colleges by ministry of education reform, to guide non-governmental higher vocational colleges of physical education reform, and the formation of the pressure of basic competition, to give private higher vocational colleges and universities sports education reform from the aspects of external motivation. (3) Optimize the general sports teaching content, improve students' comprehensive quality. Higher vocational sports education goals include not only enhance students' physical quality, include improve the students' psychological quality. Therefore, the teaching of the physical education should not only make the students master the fitness movement, motor skills as the basic method of basic sports health care. Understanding of the sports trauma treatment, basic disease prevention, exercise prescription design, basic first aid measures, such as sports health knowledge, also should make the students' ability of organization, ability to adapt and core compressive ability, self-adjustment and recovery ability and the effectively improve the comprehensive ability. (4) The innovation of sports teaching mode to cultivate the students' interest in the sports. Quality education reform is to change the past passive force-feeding teaching to active teaching and therefore, higher vocational physical education reform should also follow the same pattern. In particular, can consider break original, professional, grade, class organization, according to the different physical constitution of students and interests combined into new learning units and organizations.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00BD454C" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="3" /><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>2.4 The Sports Education Modification Orientation</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraph1st" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>Traditional college sports with current sports technology teaching as the center, in order to improve the competitive level of the means to achieve the goal of "strengthen physique". As a result of the target, the one-sided emphasis on promoting the development of students' technical ability to neglect of students' sports consciousness, sports ability, the cultivation of sports habits, played down the educational function of university sports. With the deepening reform of higher education, modern college sports from exam-oriented education to quality education transformation. Sports teaching goal by imparting the motor skills also transform in the direction of promoting students physical and mental health.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraph1st" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>Notice to deepen university sports curriculum structure reform process, will exist in the traditional curriculum structure and full of the advantages of effective mining, the innovation and development ideas combined with the traditional curriculum system advantage that play traditional colleges and the universities sports curriculum has the great development potential. "Development" is an important concept, promote new form for the university sports curriculum structure reform, development is still the fundamental principle, also is our country university sports curriculum structure reform to explore the spirit of the pursuit and it is the necessary factor to realize "innovation", the university sports curriculum structure to realize the objective of "sustainable development" the important thoughts. To this target, we propose the following suggestions as the references.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="2" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>University sports curriculum to choose interesting leisure content. College PE class time is limited, teaching content selection should consider student practice, the rational knowledge of college students is stronger, to guide it in theory and make students realize the importance of lifelong physical exercise, students interested in courses in practice, students' main body effect into the full play condition.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="2" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>University sports curriculum to build diversified curriculum system. Both junior and senior, as far as possible to the extracurricular physical education, physical education curriculum as may, by way of sports contest that will not only help students physical exercise habits, also can improve the students' ability of sports.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraphothers" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="2" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>College sports curriculum reform guided by the lifelong sports. The current college sports of curriculum can't good to meet the requirements of the new curriculum, school sports to lay a foundation for students' lifelong sports. It is the education of colleges and universities sports to its transition period, to cultivate the students' lifelong sports consciousness, must develop the students' own sports ability, stimulating the enthusiasm of students to participate in exercise.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00FB5403" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="2" /></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:lang w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">3 </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:t>Summary and Conclusion</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPParagraph1st" /><w:ind w:firstLine="240" w:firstLineChars="100" /><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /></w:rPr><w:t>In this paper, we conduct research on the development of the sports education orientation under the background of sunshine sports and quality education. Think the sunshine sports study mainly focused on the significance and the value of the sunshine sports, meanings and characteristics of the sunlight sports, such problems as how to develop sunlight sports. These studies to promote the development of sunshine sports, but also there is a theory to study the lack of rigorous logic, lack of the system and mechanism research, such as a single research method. Strengthen the sunlight sports marketing model, development of a long-term mechanism research, is not only the needs of the development of sunshine sports theory research in depth, and the sunlight sports development request inevitably. To the better implementation, our research combines the characteristics and advantages of the sunshine sports and quality education to achieve the revised physical education mode.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00CA1510" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="2" /></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>References</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00FF1F2D" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPReference" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="3" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:bookmarkStart w:name="_Ref469046486" w:id="1" /><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>Wu</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>C</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>R</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>, Jie D. "Study of the characteristics and practice guidance of girls sports teaching." 2nd International Conference on Science and Social Research (ICSSR 2013). Atlantis Press, 2013.</w:t></w:r><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="1" /></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00FF1F2D" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPReference" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="3" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:bookmarkStart w:name="_Ref469046488" w:id="2" /><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>Gao</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>P</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>J</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>, Wu Y. "Research on therapeutic methods of injured lower limbs of students majoring in sports." 2013 International Conference on Educational Research and Sports Education (ERSE 2013). Atlantis Press, 2013.</w:t></w:r><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="2" /></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00FF1F2D" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPReference" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="3" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:bookmarkStart w:name="_Ref469046513" w:id="3" /><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>Yong</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>Z. "The study of university sports education cultural system based on humanistic care." Journal of Chengdu Sport University 2011</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>;</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>3</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>:</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>22.</w:t></w:r><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="3" /></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00FF1F2D" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPReference" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="3" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:bookmarkStart w:name="_Ref469046525" w:id="4" /><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">Barboza CFS, Campello AR, Castro HC. </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>"</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>Sports, physical education, olympic games, and brazil: the deafness that still should be listened</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">." </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>Creative Education</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>2015</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>;</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>6</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>:</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>1386.</w:t></w:r><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="4" /></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00FF1F2D" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPReference" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="3" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:bookmarkStart w:name="_Ref469046527" w:id="5" /><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">White PE, Otago L, Saunders N, et al. </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>"</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>Ensuring implementation success: how should coach injury prevention education be improved if we want coaches to deliver safety programmes during training sessions?</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>"</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve"> British Journal of Sports Medicine</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>2013</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>:</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>bjsports-2012-091987.</w:t></w:r><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="5" /></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00FF1F2D" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPReference" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="3" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:bookmarkStart w:name="_Ref469046539" w:id="6" /><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">Tikhonova NV. </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>"</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>Significance of youth and sports in Ukraine backup for the education of the younger generation</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">." </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>Pedagogics, Psychology, Medical-biological Problems of Physical Training and Sports</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve"> </w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>2014</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>;</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>9.</w:t></w:r><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="6" /></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="008F6B80" w:rsidP="00FF1F2D" w:rsidRDefault="008F6B80"><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="TTPReference" /><w:numPr><w:ilvl w:val="0" /><w:numId w:val="3" /></w:numPr><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:bookmarkStart w:name="_Ref469046554" w:id="7" /><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>Zhu H</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>D</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>. "The Building of sports e-education platform using multimedia technology." International Journal of Digital Content Technology &amp; its Applications 2012</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>;</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" /></w:rPr><w:t>6</w:t></w:r><w:r><w:rPr><w:color w:val="000000" /><w:lang w:val="en-US" w:eastAsia="zh-CN" /></w:rPr><w:t>.</w:t></w:r><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="7" /></w:p><w:sectPr w:rsidR="008F6B80"><w:headerReference w:type="even" r:id="rId10" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" /><w:headerReference w:type="default" r:id="rId11" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" /><w:pgSz w:w="11907" w:h="16840" /><w:pgMar w:top="1418" w:right="1134" w:bottom="851" w:left="1134" w:header="709" w:footer="284" w:gutter="0" /><w:cols w:space="720" /></w:sectPr></w:body>